http://www.extol.com/privacy-notice

Skip to main content
Cleo Privacy NoticeCleo respects your right to privacy. This policy summarizes what personally identifiable information we may collect and how we might use this information. This policy also describes other important topics relating to your privacy.Information CollectionCleo only collects personally identifiable information, such as name, title, company name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address that you voluntarily provide through our website or email correspondence. We will collect general information, such as the type of browser you use, the files you request, and the domain name and country from which you request information, to improve our website and better meet your needs.Use of InformationBefore we collect any personally identifiable information, we will provide an explanation for the possible use of your data. The information you supply will be used by Cleo to respond to your inquiries, supply you with requested information on Cleo products and services, or track orders you place with Cleo. Authorized third parties may be utilized by Cleo to collect, track and process such information. By requesting information and/or completing online and campaign based forms, you will automatically be opted-in to receive information on Cleo promotions, product releases, technical topics, and more.Cleo complies with the CAN-SPAM act of 2003. If you have submitted personal information to Cleo electronically and would like it removed or modified, please contact us at +1 815.282.7695 or complete the unsubscribe request for automatic removal. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request.Use of Cookies: How Cleo Uses Cookies on the SiteA cookie is a small amount of information that a website copies onto your hard drive. A cookie can help a website identify you the next time you visit it.Cleo uses cookies to improve the quality of your experience through features such as personalization and customization. Additionally, we use cookies for user analysis, enabling us to better understand how our users look for information when they arrive at the Cleo site. This information is aggregated and used to constantly improve the usability and information structure of our site.We also use cookies to provide special access to password-protected areas of the site to qualified customers, partners and internal users. By using cookies, Cleo’s site will recognize your password each time you return so that you will not need to log in again. If you would like to access the site from another computer, you will need to enter your user name and password again when entering protected areas.You must have the preferences in your browser set to accept cookies. We keep any information that you provide while registering or that we obtained from the use of cookies strictly confidential. The information is used for internal purposes only, helping us to improve services for our clients. Because information obtained from the use of cookies applies only to the Cleo website, and because we do not share this information with other sites, your browsing behavior cannot be “tracked” by Cleo once you leave our site.Children and ParentsCleo does not intend to collect personally identifiable information from children under age 13 without permission of the child’s parent or legal guardian. Children under the age of 13 should submit personally identifiable information to Cleo only with the explicit permission of their parent or legal guardian. Where appropriate, Cleo will instruct children not to submit personal information. If your child has submitted personal information and you would like to request that such information be removed, you may do so by calling +1 815.282.7695.Other Important InformationThe Cleo website may contain links to other sites. We do not endorse or otherwise accept responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those sites. Additionally, some of our web pages may contain “cookies,” which are data that may be sent to your web browser and stored on your computer. This allows our server to “recognize” you when you visit our website in the future. Most web browsers can be configured to not accept cookies, or to notify you if a cookie is sent to you. It may be necessary, if required by law or if pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations, to release your personally identifiable information. Cleo reserves the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. We will promptly reflect any such modifications in these web pages.
Connect with Cleo We’re here to help you. Leverage Cleo integration experts to help you find the right solution for your integration needs. Whether you are looking to modernize your integration, consolidate your systems, or simply looking for an easier way to integrate your ecosystem, Cleo has you covered.
CONTACT US
REQUEST A DEMO
SUBSCRIBE TO OUR BLOG
Talk to us. Tell us how we can help or contact Sales at 815.282.7695 for immediate assistance.
First Name*Last Name*CompanyPhoneOffice Email*Country*-- Please Select --United StatesAngolaArgentinaArubaAustraliaAustriaBahamasBangladeshBelgiumBosniaBrazilBulgariaCanadaChileChinaColombiaCosta RicaCroatiaCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEthiopiaFinlandFranceGeorgiaGermanyGreeceHaitiHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIraqIrelandIsraelItalyJapanJerseyJordanKenyaKorea, Republic ofKuwaitLatviaLebanonLibyaLiechtensteinLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMalaysiaMaltaMexicoMonacoMongoliaMoroccoNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew ZealandNigeriaNorwayPakistanPanamaPapua New GuineaPeruPhilippinesPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRussian FederationSaint Kitts and NevisSaudi ArabiaSerbiaSingaporeSloveniaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSpainSri LankaSwedenSwitzerlandTaiwan, Province of ChinaTanzaniaThailandTunisiaTurkeyUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States Minor Outlying IslandsUruguayVenezuelaViet NamVirgin Islands (British)Virgin Islands (U.S.)State or Province-- Please Select ---ABAKALARASAZBCCACOCTDCDEFLFMGAGUHIIAIDILINKSKYLAMAMBMDMEMHMIMNMOMPMSMTNBNCNDNENHNJNLNMNSNTNUNVNYOHOKONORPAPEPRPWQCRISCSDSKTNTXUTVAVIVTWAWIWVWYYTState or Province-- Please Select --ABBCMBNBNLNSNTNUONPEQCSKYTQuestion/Need*Cleo will send you occasional emails, you may unsubscribe at any time. Cleo Privacy Policy.
Request a Free Demo Request a custom demo or contact Sales at 815.282.7695 for immediate assistance.
Office Email*First NameLast NameCompanyPhoneCountry-- Please Select --United StatesAngolaArgentinaArubaAustraliaAustriaBahamasBangladeshBelgiumBosniaBrazilBulgariaCanadaChileChinaColombiaCosta RicaCroatiaCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEthiopiaFinlandFranceGeorgiaGermanyGreeceHaitiHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIraqIrelandIsraelItalyJapanJerseyJordanKenyaKorea, Republic ofKuwaitLatviaLebanonLibyaLiechtensteinLithuanisLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMalaysiaMaltaMexicoMonacoMongoliaMoroccoNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew ZealandNigeriaNorwayPakistanPanamaPapua New GuineaPeruPhilippinesPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRussian FederationSaint Kitts and NevisSaudi ArabiaSerbiaSingaporeSloveniaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSpainSri LankaSwedenSwitzerlandTaiwan, Province of ChinaTanzaniaThailandTunisiaTurkeyUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States Minor Outlying IslandsUruguayVenezuelaViet NamVirgin Islands (British)Virgin Islands (U.S.)State or Province-- Please Select ---ABAKALARASAZBCCACOCTDCDEFLFMGAGUHIIAIDILINKSKYLAMAMBMDMEMHMIMNMOMPMSMTNBNCNDNENHNJNLNMNSNTNUNVNYOHOKONORPAPEPRPWQCRISCSDSKTNTXUTVAVIVTWAWIWVWYYTState or Province-- Please Select --ABBCMBNBNLNSNTNUONPEQCSKYTAre there specific areas you would like to cover in a demo?sourceCleo will send you occasional emails, you may unsubscribe at any time. Cleo Privacy Policy.
Subscribe to Blog Get our latest and greatest blogs in your inbox every other week!
Office Email*Cleo will send you occasional emails, you may unsubscribe at any time. Cleo Privacy Policy.
